articledeck.com 2012-09-19

# Article Deck - your Free Article directory, submit & find Articles- free Article directory

### Privacy Policy Overview

This Privacy Policy covers the ArticleDeck treatment of personal information that is recorded when you submit an article, or request an article via email. Other than the information requested in our online forms, no other information is collected from visitors to our web site.

Our privacy policy does not apply to the practices of other companies advertised, or otherwise listed, on the ArticleDeck web site, nor does it extend to people that ArticleDeck does not employ or manage.

### Author Anonymity

ArticleDeck does not provide or guarantee author anonymity. Authors who wish to remain anonymous should either **NOT** complete the Author Profile in their member accounts **OR** complete it using a Pen Name.

Although discovering an Author's real identity is difficult if a Pen Name is used in submitting articles, there are several ways for that information to be found if the Author Profile is completed with your real name and identity details.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

ArticleDeck maintains your email address and other pertinent information in a secure database. Your contact information is never released or sold to any vendor, partner or outside agency. ArticleDeck, however, reserves the right to contact ArticleDeck members via email as deemed necessary. Such mailings will always include detailed unsubscribe information, providing members the option of removing themselves from future ArticleDeck mailings at any time.

### Security

Your email address information is stored in a protected directory. Access is restricted to ArticleDeck staff.

### Information Collection

ArticleDeck collects minimal personal information when you request or submit an article. The only information collected in these instances is your name, email address, IP address and the date of your request or submission.

### Information Use

If you are ArticleDeck Author member, your use of our service constitutes a business relationship wherein we provide a promotion service for your article(s). In exchange, ArticleDeck reserves the right to use the contact information collected during member registration to deliver notices regarding changes or updates to our service, to provide a free newsletter, to inform you of additions to ArticleDeck, or to send announcements and carefully screened offers and information on behalf of our partners or advertisers.

You may remove yourself from any or all of our mailings at anytime using the unsubscribe methods provided in those mailings. Any mailing received from our company is clearly identified and includes a valid email address and unsubscribe link which you can use to remove yourself from future mailings. Should you encounter problems in this regard, contact us.

Spam complaints will result in membership termination.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

ArticleDeck may amend this policy from time to time. If significant changes are made in the way your personal information is used, we will post a prominent announcement on our site notifying you of the change.

Author Articles

More From This Author

Amitech USA, Ltd. is a member of one the world's leading pipe technology and manufacturing companies. Â The Amiantit Group is an international organization with a track record of growth-orientated...

After the Attorney General of Massachusetts promulgated comprehensive regulations governing the advertising and sale of cigarettes, smokeless tobacco, and cigars, petitioners, a group of tobacco...

Petitioner sought to fill wetlands for beach front subdivision, which Rhode Island Coastal Resources Management Council rejected, ruling that the proposal did not satisfy the standards for...

Petitioner was ordered deported for his criminal record. No country would accept him and Cambodia did not have a repatriation treaty. He challenged his detention indefinitely as...

The Mushroom Promotion, Research, and Consumer Information Act mandates that fresh mushroom handlers pay assessments used primarily to fund advertisements promoting mushroom sales. Respondent...

Related Articles

Related Articles

Being branded as a punk stylist is not an easy thing in the modern world, where fashion is more about designer clothes than the half torn shirts, haircuts, piercings, and much more. With new designs...

A couch is a sofa, normally heavily cushioned. They are normally pieces of furniture with seating attunements for two and more people. Some couches are strictly single setters. An electric couch,...

Nobody can determine our lifetime how is to generally be although we will try to acquire our seek to improve our daily life. Similarly the accidents are very important issue whenever it happens to us...

Fashion is something that keeps changing everytime. If one fabric or design is in fashion then it is likely to change next week. People who are fed up visiting markets to find something fresh and ...

Fashion and style keep on changing as they define the human state of mind which also keeps on changing from time to time. These changes are inevitable and that is why the changes in the style...

Latest Articles

Latest Articles

If you are the owner of a business that have been established in recent times, you are probably aware of the fact that it is extremely important to have an online existence of that business. In case...

In the twentieth century, the internet has been powerful equipment. It has created a new world. Millions of users are here to do different types of activities. And in the world, usually there is no...

All the general mediums of advertising are getting clogged up and crowded. So, where the marketers will go? Will they continue with the same policy of continuously pushing and struggling on that same...

When we are driving down a long highway, an expressway or even the congest city streets, we always come across some really large and colorful hoardings, gigantic screens and billboards that attract...

World over products are manufactured by several companies, but only a few could really do better in the actual marketplace. Applying proper marketing techniques could make a star performer in the...

Most Read Articles

Most Read Articles

Mothers Day Poems Mother when you're not I regarÃ© with my tears oh mother! the garden the House and the yard malvones; It will be when your absence palpiten Geraniums and cry the gardenias and...

How To Save A Marriage: The 5 Steps To Discuss a Disagreement That Wonâ€™t Make Things Worse 1\. Donâ€™t keep score. When youâ€™re discussing a disagreement, itâ€™s natural to try to â€œwinâ€...

Phpbb is essential in website management and designing. Most hosting websites require that you download phpbb before accessing their site to run your own page. When looking for a phpbb hosting...

In the half-century that has followed Kirsten and his family has revolutionized the game of golf with passion, engineering skills and a desire to seek innovation and demand quality. To celebrate...
